<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://kentuckyroutezero.com/KRZConversation.xslt"?>
<conversation act="one">
  <scene name="intro">
    <triggerEvent name="meet-carrington"/>
    <setGameVar name="met-carrington" value="true"/>
    
    <line speaker="joseph">... and that's only a few miles outside of Hodgenville anyway. I don't think you could do much better for accessibility, and they got that new gas station if folks get lost —</line>
    <line speaker="carrington">But maybe they `should` feel lost, Joseph: just as lost then as we are always already lost. Just like poor, itinerant Silas, wandering the road, looking for a home.</line>
    <line speaker="joseph">Well that's a way to look at it, I guess ...</line>
    <line speaker="joseph">`(To CONWAY.)` Well, hello! I heard that old truck rumble on up. How's {if}[dog-nameless]that dog{end}{if}[!dog-nameless]${dog-name}{end}? Say, maybe you can help this fellow. He's looking for a ... a &quot;venue&quot; is how you said it, right?</line>
    <option goto="bar-stage" speaker="conway">Sure, I have an old friend who runs a bar, and they've got a real big stage.</option>
    <option goto="furniture-warehouse" speaker="conway">Sure, I know a furniture warehouse you could probably break into.</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="bar-stage" nextScene="introduce-play">
    <line speaker="carrington">No, no, it can't be indoors. Impossible ...</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="furniture-warehouse" nextScene="introduce-play">
    <line speaker="carrington">This isn't some illegal drug party!</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="introduce-play">
    <line speaker="carrington">But I'm obliged you'd stop a moment to help me work this through. Let me explain my charge:</line>
    <line speaker="carrington">I've dedicated my last twelve years to the design and orchestration of my life's great work: a grand, broadly experimental theatrical adaptation of `The Death of the Hired Man` by Robert Frost.</line>
    <option goto="more-hired-man" speaker="conway">Yeah, I've read some of his stuff.</option>
    <option goto="experimental" speaker="conway">How do you mean &quot;experimental&quot;?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="more-hired-man" nextScene="experimental">
    <line speaker="joseph">Yeah, he's pretty OK. Not one of my favorites. But Carrington here has a knack for drama!</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="experimental">
    <line speaker="carrington">Well, drama is really my `second` love. My higher calling is Pseudoscience.</line>
    <option goto="pseudoscience" speaker="conway">Yep. Pseudoscience.</option>
    <option goto="performance-time" speaker="conway">So when is the performance?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="pseudoscience" nextScene="performance-time">
    <line speaker="carrington">Pseudoscience is the eternally fruitful marriage of whimsy and process that has yielded such poetic specimens as: astrology, phrenology, canals on mars, and homeopathic medicine.</line>
    <line speaker="carrington">I hope I have the time to explain how my pseudoscientific theory-poetics find expression in this play, but now I am in a delirious rush ...</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="performance-time">
    <line speaker="carrington">The event is to be performed tomorrow morning, just before dawn. But, in the spirit of tragedy, our venue fell through at the last moment. I've been out all day driving the highways looking for a replacement, eyes fastened to the landscape, like a hawk scouring the field.</line>
    <line speaker="carrington">So like a hawk, in fact, that I failed to keep an eye on my gas meter. I'm here waiting for the tow truck to bring my car so I can get back at the task.</line>
    <option goto="good-spots" speaker="conway">Well, I don't mind keeping an eye out for a spot; I'm on a drive anyway.</option>
    <option goto="what-kind-of-venue" speaker="conway">So what kind of venue are you looking for?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="good-spots" nextScene="end">
    <line speaker="carrington">If you have attention to spare, I'd be grateful. Somewhere outdoors. Somewhere intimate. Somewhere tragic.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="what-kind-of-venue" nextScene="end">
    <line speaker="carrington">Somewhere outdoors. Somewhere intimate. Somewhere tragic. If you have attention to spare on your drive, I'd be grateful.</line>
  </scene>

</conversation>
