<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://kentuckyroutezero.com/KRZConversation.xslt"?>
<conversation act="one">
  <scene name="intro">
    <setGameVar name="spoke-with-shannon-at-farmhouse" value="true"/>
    
    <line speaker="shannon">So, this is where she was? Yeah, makes sense. This was where Weaver and her parents lived. They took out a bunch of loans, you know, and had this place built.</line>
    <line speaker="shannon">Do you have any debts?</line>
    <option goto="collateral" speaker="conway">I never really had any collateral.</option>
    <option goto="apologies" speaker="conway">I owe some people some apologies.</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="apologies" nextScene="debt">
    <line speaker="shannon">Well, you're lucky that's all you owe.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="collateral" nextScene="debt">
    <line speaker="shannon">Something to be said for that, I guess.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="debt">
    <line speaker="shannon">My parents were like that. Until the company store found a way to get to them. For my dad it was tokens to run the fans and air purifiers, and for my mom it was canaries. Two solutions to the same problem, but they sure sounded different.</line>
    <line speaker="shannon">Weaver had debt, too — a lot of it. All tuition.</line>
    <option goto="pay-off" speaker="conway">How did she pay it off?</option>
    <option goto="mathematician" speaker="conway">She said she was a mathematician or something?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="pay-off" nextScene="bills">
    <line speaker="shannon">She didn't. She had no income, none of them did.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="mathematician" nextScene="bills">
    <line speaker="shannon">Yeah, she studied some esoteric stuff about ... something about using math to translate between Spanish and English?</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="bills">
    <line speaker="shannon">I think eventually Weaver put those math skills to work on all the red numbers in the family checkbook, and got a clear sense of just how hopeless their situation was.</line>
    <line speaker="shannon">So she left. I guess she just drove away in the middle of the night — they woke up in the morning and the car was gone. Never came back.</line>
    <line speaker="shannon">Until tonight.</line>
    
    <option goto="someone-else" speaker="conway">Someone else told me to come here and talk to her.</option>
    <option goto="old-tv" speaker="conway">She seemed really focused on that old TV.</option>
    <option goto="happy-to-see-her" speaker="conway">Were you happy to see her?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="someone-else" nextScene="old-tv">
    <line speaker="shannon">Huh. OK. I guess we two aren't the only ones she's been talking to.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="happy-to-see-her" nextScene="old-tv">
    <line speaker="shannon">I don't know. It was so sudden and ... it wasn't like a reunion. She just appeared. She —</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="old-tv" nextScene="end">
    <line speaker="shannon">Oh. That's not something you see every day. That old TV right there, well, `that` is a damned antique for you. I had a model like that in the shop once, but I had to sell it off to make rent. Most painful decision I ever made.</line>
    <line speaker="shannon">Say, do you mind if I open it up? Looks like the dials are all corroded, and the screen is leaking light a bit. Come on — I bet Lysette would never forgive you for letting a specimen like that fall into disrepair.</line>
  </scene>

</conversation>