<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://kentuckyroutezero.com/KRZConversation.xslt"?>
<conversation act="one" endingEvent="shack-conversation-end">
  <scene name="intro" nextScene="desk">
    <triggerEvent name="enter-shack"/>
    <setGameVar name="elkhorn-valley-outro-complete" value="true"/>
    
    <line>The cramped shack is lined with wooden shelves. Dusty stacks of tape reels and notebooks crowd the room, but a bit of moonlight filters through a window near the ceiling.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="desk" nextScene="choose-notebook">
    <line pause="false">On a small desk in the middle of the room lay three notebooks. The red one is labeled &quot;J. Márquez,&quot; the green one is labeled &quot;R. Márquez,&quot; and the blue one is unlabeled.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="choose-notebook">
    <goto condition="elkhorn-mine-outro-read-green-notebook+elkhorn-mine-outro-read-blue-notebook" sceneName="red-notebook-interrupt"/>
    <goto condition="elkhorn-mine-outro-read-red-notebook+elkhorn-mine-outro-read-blue-notebook" sceneName="green-notebook-interrupt"/>
    <goto condition="elkhorn-mine-outro-read-red-notebook+elkhorn-mine-outro-read-green-notebook" sceneName="blue-notebook-interrupt"/>    
    
    <option condition="!elkhorn-mine-outro-read-red-notebook" goto="red-notebook" insertedText="Conway opens the red notebook.">Open the red notebook.</option>
    <option condition="!elkhorn-mine-outro-read-green-notebook" goto="green-notebook" insertedText="Conway opens the green notebook.">Open the green notebook.</option>
    <option condition="!elkhorn-mine-outro-read-blue-notebook" goto="blue-notebook" insertedText="Conway opens the blue notebook.">Open the blue notebook.</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="red-notebook" nextScene="choose-notebook">
    <triggerEvent name="shannon-exits-mine-to-shack"/>
    <setGameVar name="elkhorn-mine-outro-read-red-notebook" value="true"/>

    <line>The pages are covered in disorganized notes, some written horizontally and others scribbled vertically into margins. A few pages are lined more evenly and divided up into charts correlating seasons, lyrics, harmonies, and coal hauls.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="green-notebook" nextScene="choose-notebook">
    <triggerEvent name="shannon-exits-mine-to-shack"/>    
    <setGameVar name="elkhorn-mine-outro-read-green-notebook" value="true"/>

    <line>On each page is a delicately-rendered charcoal drawing. Most are portraits of rugged faces. Near the middle of the book, there are a few drawings of a young girl in a miner's helmet. She plays along the mine cart tracks, collecting pieces of wire. In one drawing, another young girl sits nearby, intently studying a book.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="blue-notebook" nextScene="choose-notebook">
    <triggerEvent name="shannon-exits-mine-to-shack"/>    
    <setGameVar name="elkhorn-mine-outro-read-blue-notebook" value="true"/>

    <line>The notebook is full of greek letters and cryptic mathematical formulas. Near the back of the book, what first looks like it might be an esoteric German shorthand is actually a love poem written in anagrams.</line>
  </scene>

  <!-- Notebook interruption versions -->
  <scene name="red-notebook-interrupt" nextScene="shannon-enters-shack">
    <line>Conway opens the red notebook.</line>
    <line>The pages are covered in disorganized notes, some written horizontally and others scribbled vertically into margins. A few pages are lined more evenly and divided up into —</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="green-notebook-interrupt" nextScene="shannon-enters-shack">
    <line>Conway opens the green notebook.</line>    
    <line>On each page is a delicately-rendered charcoal drawing. Most are portraits of rugged faces. Near the middle of the book, there are a few drawings of a young girl in a miner's helmet. She plays along the mine cart tracks, collecting pieces of —</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="blue-notebook-interrupt" nextScene="shannon-enters-shack">
    <line>Conway opens the blue notebook.</line>    
    <line>The notebook is full of Greek letters and cryptic mathematical formulas. Near the back of the book, what first looks like it might be —</line>
  </scene>

  <!-- Shannon enters shack -->
  <scene name="shannon-enters-shack">
    <line speaker="shannon">Oh yeah. This place.</line>
    
    <option goto="didnt-think-coming" speaker="conway">I didn't think you were coming back.</option>
    <option goto="archivists-parents" speaker="conway">These notebooks are labeled &quot;Márquez.&quot; Your parents are the archivists?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="didnt-think-coming">
    <line speaker="shannon">Sure I was. Why wouldn't I be?</line>
    
    <option goto="disappearing" speaker="conway">Most everyone else I've met tonight has just disappeared.</option>
    <option goto="looking-for" speaker="conway">Did you find what you were looking for?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="disappearing" nextScene="intro-more-options">
    <line pause="false" speaker="shannon">Well here I am, dammit.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="looking-for" nextScene="intro-more-options">
    <line pause="false" speaker="shannon">Yeah ... Maybe. Look, we're not going to talk about that anymore, OK?</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="intro-more-options">
    <option goto="intro-sorry" speaker="conway">Sorry.</option>
    <option goto="archivists-parents" speaker="conway">The notebooks are labeled &quot;Márquez.&quot; Your parents are the archivists?</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="archivists-parents" nextScene="leg">
    <line speaker="shannon">No. Weaver's parents are the archivists. My parents were miners.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="intro-sorry" nextScene="leg">
    <line speaker="shannon">No, I'm sorry. I'm just on edge. I'll be OK once I get away from this mine.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="leg">
    <line speaker="shannon">... How's the leg?</line>
    <option goto="leg-slow" speaker="conway">I can walk on it, but it's slow.</option>
    <option goto="leg-painful" speaker="conway">I can walk on it, but it's painful.</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="leg-slow" nextScene="shannon-drive">
    <line speaker="shannon">Well, I'll try not to get too far ahead of you. You don't mind my hitching a ride, do you? I kinda got a lift out here, and wasn't sure if, uh — when I'd be heading back. I can drive.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="leg-painful" nextScene="shannon-drive">
    <setGameVar name="shannon-gave-painkillers" value="true"/>    
    <line speaker="shannon">Oh. I've got some painkillers here that could help you out. I got them from a friend when I sprained my wrist installing a security system. You'd better let me drive, though. They're pretty strong.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="shannon-drive">
    <option goto="conway-will-drive" speaker="conway">I can handle it.</option>
    <option goto="shannon-will-drive" speaker="conway">Yeah, maybe that's best.</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="conway-will-drive" nextScene="next-steps">
    <line pause="false" speaker="shannon">OK. Your decision.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="shannon-will-drive" nextScene="next-steps">
    <setGameVar name="shannon-will-drive" value="true"/>
    <line pause="false" speaker="shannon">Don't worry: I've been driving since I was nine.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="next-steps">
    <option goto="zero" speaker="conway">I still need to find the |Zero|.</option>
    <option goto="dogwood" speaker="conway">I guess I should look for another route to Dogwood Drive.</option>
  </scene>

  <scene name="zero" nextScene="find-weaver">
    <line speaker="shannon">Well, it's like I told you: Weaver doesn't lie. If she sent you here to find your on-ramp, this is where you should be looking. Or maybe you just weren't listening closely enough, and that's not exactly what she said?</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="dogwood" nextScene="find-weaver">
    <line speaker="shannon">Yeah, alright. Well, maybe asking Weaver about the |Zero| was the wrong place to start. Maybe we should just ask her for specific directions. Her answers are complicated enough without a layer of indirection at the question.</line>
  </scene>

  <scene name="find-weaver" nextScene="end">
    <line speaker="shannon">I saw Weaver at my workshop. That's up north by Lake Nolin, right at Wax and Peonia, in the back of a bait shop. Pretty glamorous, right? These are the times we live in.</line>
    <line speaker="shannon">She's either up there or back at the farmhouse. Whichever you want to head to first, just let me know.</line>
  </scene>

</conversation>
